{
  "response_code": 0,
  "results": [
    {
      "category": "General Knowledge",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Who is cso HOD?",
      "correct_answer": "Nagamalleswara Rao",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Nageswararo", "Prudhvi", "Nagaraju"]
    },
    {
      "category": "General Knowledge",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Who got first rank in IoT 1st year?",
      "correct_answer": "Indra Prakash",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Ramesh", "Yodha", "Shanmukh"]
    },
    {
      "category": "General Knowledge",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Who got selected for NCC from iot?",
      "correct_answer": "Rajasekhar",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Harishankar",
        "Prabhas",
        "Vinay"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "General Knowledge",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Who is the principal of college?",
      "correct_answer": "Kolla Srinivas",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Ravindra",
        "Sudhakar",
        "Prasad"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "General Knowledge",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Iot department is in which block?",
      "correct_answer": "Hi-Tech",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Cyber", "SJB", "Digital"]
    },
    {
      "category": "General Knowledge",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "What is the room number for iot 3rd year??",
      "correct_answer": "114",
      "incorrect_answers": ["112", "111", "110"]
    },
    {
      "category": "General Knowledge",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Who is class teacher for iot 3rd year??",
      "correct_answer": "Prudhvi",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Nagamalleswara rao",
        "Nageswara rao",
        "Nagaraju"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "General Knowledge",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Who is lover boy in IoT third year ?",
      "correct_answer": "Anirudh",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Yodha", "Srinu", "Shanmukh"]
    },
    {
      "category": "General Knowledge",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "How many faculty are in IOT department",
      "correct_answer": "4",
      "incorrect_answers": ["1", "5", "3"]
    },
    {
      "category": "General Knowledge",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "What is Indra Surname?",
      "correct_answer": "Gottipati",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Ravintula", "Kotla", "Pamarthi"]
    }
  ]
}
